# Irfan Fazal Irfanfazal03@gmail.com



## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To contribute towards the growth and development of Information Technology where there are opportunities to grow both professionally and personally and where I can utilize and develop my skills and experience efficiently, and serve my community effectively.

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Name	:	Irfan Fazal
Father Name	:	Muhammad Fazal Khan
Postal Address	:	Muhammad Fazal TS near Madina Market Bagh A.K
Current Address		Sahlian Maldialan Tehsil and district Bagh A.K
Cell #	:	+923478092378
Nationality	:	Pakistani
Domicile	:	Bagh(A.K)
Date of birth	:	23-11-1992
E-mail	:	irfanfazal03@gmail.com

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

- 2 Year of Experience in Web Design and Development.
  - **ERPIN Technologies Private Limited (Rawalpindi)**

Worked as a ASP.NET Developer.

## Solume Science Technologies (Rawalpindi)

Completed one year internship as a Software Developer since July 2017 to July 2018.

## Medical Transcription billing company (MTBC)

**Tenure: December 2018 to Present** 

Doing job as a software Engineer at MTBC Bagh office.

#### ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

#### **BS(Computer Science) (BSCS)**

(2012-16)

CGPA: 3.82 Percentage: 80.4

University of Azad Jammu & Kashmir

#### **Final Year Project Name:**

## Online system for UAJ&K Testing Service

### HSSC (Mathematics, Physics, Computer) (2008-2010)

National Science College Bagh A.K (Mirpur Board)

Division & Percentage: 1st div /78%

## SSC Group Science (Physics, Chemistry, Biology) (2006-2008)

F.G Public High School Bagh A.K (Federal Board Islamabad)

Division & Percentage: 1st div /68 %

#### CERTIFICATIONS IN WEB DEVELOPMENT

#### **Web Designing & Development (4 Months)**

EVS Learning Center (Rawalpindi)

#### **CERTIFICATIONS IN NETWORKING**

#### **❖** CISCO CERTIFIED NETWORK ASSOCIATE (CCNA)

AT EZXPERT RAWALPINDI.

## **❖** MICROSOFT CERTIFIED SOLUTION EXPERT (MCSE)

AT EZXPERT RAWALPINDI.

#### **❖ MICROSOFT CERTIFIED OFFICE SPECIALIST (MOS)**

#### KEY SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Ability to Adapt in New Organization or Place.
- Able to work as a part of team.
- Reliable and Punctual.
- Approachable and friendly.
- Hardworking.
- Excellent communication skills.

#### COMPUTER SKILLS

Able to work in Microsoft applicant atmosphere/projects with confidence and able to run any software after taking some time to learn its logic.

## **Proficient in**

- Microsoft office
- Programming in Borland.
- Static web development in Notepad
- Good understanding of Asp.net Architecture and Development
- Angular JS
- Angular 2,4 and 6
- Asp.net Web API's
- Microsoft SQL server 2014
- Bootstrap
- HTML
- JQuery

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Obtaining a laptop under PMNL laptop Scheme based on academic scores.
- Served as a C.R(Class Representative )(2012-2016).
- Obtaining an Appreciation card from **AL-Quresh Welfare Foundation** for good scores in intermediate.

•

## **HOBBIES**

- Playing Cricket
- Reading books like Islamic and Pakistan history
- Reading newspapers

## REFERENCES

Will be provided upon request

THANKS FOR KEEPING THIS QUERY CONFIDENTIAL